my whole family is nuts i remember my
aunt she used to make
embroidered inspirational pillows yeah
one day she smothered my uncle with one
of them
the last thing he saw coming at him was
today is the first day of the rest of
your
life
she was mean she used to try to curse
people she used to try to give him the
evil
eye but unfortunately she had a lazy eye
so she just kind of spread it all over
the room and
no one was really cursed everyone just
had a little trouble parking
and i have to apologize because i didn't
know
sometimes i say oh my god and the first
crowd kind of didn't like it so i want
to apologize i don't mean any disrespect
it just comes out of my mouth very
easily so if that happens just go
huh she's nuts
and on the way out if offends you i'll
be there you can punch me lightly
one punch for every time i said that
there now that's out of the way and i
won't swear anymore either
uh i don't want to be arrested
[Laughter]
this side of the room likes the jokes a
lot more this style aroma
this side is like a rester
[Music]
oh my god but this is what you do
oh and then i said it
wow they kept saying it comes right out
of your mouth and i was like no it
doesn't
this is what you gotta do folks you
gotta get out you gotta
enjoy life you can't worry you certainly
can't worry about money
i know you all look up here you see the
bright lights
in my two dollar goodwill dress and
you say who is she to tell us not to
worry about
money when she looks like she's rich
and you guys would be surprised i'm not
in fact i am 90 000 in debt and i don't
have a care in the world
because that's what you do you get so
far in debt then it's
visa's problem not yours
you know shame on them for giving me
that credit in the first place
i think someone should be fired
and i haven't paid my credit card bills
in over a year
but they still send me one every month
and you know why because those people
believe in me
that's right they think i'm gonna hit it
big and pay them back
in fact they care so much they even
called me at home
they did they said karen could you send
us just a little each month
and i said no
but don't worry i've already forgiven
myself
[Music]
i won't let this affect my self-esteem
[Applause]
local man robs wendy's with alligator
for the alligator boys now
the bank should be going mom mom